<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreenDefend</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_onboarding1">Find out the types of diseases Various plants</string>
    <string name="disception_onboarding1">Plant disease diagnosis is now within reach everyone</string>
    <string name="started_now">started now</string>
    <string name="title_onboarding2">Treat your plant from home security</string>
    <string name="disception_onboarding2">Plant treatment has become easier with the application</string>
    <string name="title_onboarding3">Provide plant specific treatment depending on the disease</string>
    <string name="disception_onboarding3">Find out the effective treatment of the plant with just a click in our application</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="green">Green</string>
    <string name="e_mail">E-mail</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_your_password">Forgot your password</string>
    <string name="remember">Remember</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an account</string>
    <string name="or_through">Or through</string>
    <string name="phone_or_email">" Email"</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="enter_code">Enter code</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="account_has_been_created_successfully">account has been created successfully</string>
    <string name="you_can_browse_the_application_now_with_knowledge_about_farming">You can browse the application now with knowledge about farming</string>
    <string name="defend">Defend</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="know_your_plant_s_disease_and_treat_it_easily">Know the disease of your plant and treat it easily</string>
    <string name="threat">threat</string>
    <string name="upload_image">upload image</string>
    <string name="create_new_account">Create new account</string>
    <string name="enter_the_code_sent_to_the_email">Enter the code sent to the email</string>
    <string name="code_validation">code validation</string>
    <string name="weather_today">Weather today</string>
    <string name="february_3_new_damietta_city">February 3. New Damietta City</string>
    <string name="_18_c">18°C</string>
    <string name="sunset_5_30pm">Sunset 5.30pm</string>
    <string name="the_weather_is_cloudy_today_and_sunny_at_times_n_today_is_a_bad_day_to_use_pesticides">The weather is cloudy today, and sunny at times\n Today is a bad day to use pesticides</string>
    <string name="crop_information">Crop information</string>
    <string name="plant_diseases">Plant diseases</string>
    <string name="plant_observation">Plant observation</string>
    <string name="diagnostic_tips">Diagnostic tips</string>
    <string name="_1_bring_the_camera_close_to_the_plant_and_make_sure_that_the_disease_spreading_in_the_plant_is_visible_within_the_frame">1 - Bring the camera close to the plant and make sure that the disease spreading in the plant is visible within the frame</string>
    <string name="_2_make_sure_that_the_camera_correctly_shows_the_disease_present_in_the_plant">2- Make sure that the camera correctly shows the disease present in the plant</string>
    <string name="_3_make_sure_that_the_plant_is_visible_and_that_it_is_not_too_dark_or_too_bright">3- Make sure that the plant is visible and that it is not too dark or too bright</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="it_s_cloudy_today">It\'s cloudy today</string>
    <string name="today_is_a_bad_day_to_use_pesticides">Today is a bad day to use pesticides</string>
    <string name="weather_for_the_coming_days">Weather for the coming days</string>
    <string name="ask_the_community">Ask the community</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add image</string>
    <string name="ask_the_community_and_receive_answers_from_experts">Ask the community and receive answers from experts</string>
    <string name="add_a_question_indicating_the_problem_facing_your_crop">Add a question indicating the problem facing your crop</string>
    <string name="what_does_it_take_for_a_potato_to_grow_well_knowing_that_it_has_about_50_days_in_yellowing_of_leaves">What does it take for a potato to grow well, knowing that it has about 50 days? In yellowing of leaves</string>
    <string name="enter_the_required_data_below">Enter the required data below</string>
    <string name="enter_first_name">Enter First Name</string>
    <string name="enter_middle_name">Enter middle name</string>
    <string name="enter_last_name">Enter Last name</string>
    <string name="enter_phone_number">Enter phone number</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="profile">profile</string>
    <string name="home">home</string>
    <string name="forum">Forum</string>
    <string name="search_the_forum">Search the forum</string>
    <string name="please_allow_permission_on_camera">please allow permission on camera</string>
    <string name="green_defend">Green Defend</string>
    <string name="finished">Finished</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="give_an_introduction_about_yourself_to_others">Give an introduction about yourself to others</string>
    <string name="chage">Chage</string>
    <string name="treat_your_plant_safely_with_growers_of_the_world">Treat your plant safely with growers of the world</string>
    <string name="share_green_defend_with_your_friends_and_help_develop_agriculture_and_plant_protection">Share Green Defend with your friends and help develop agriculture and plant protection</string>
    <string name="share_green_defend">Share Green Defend</string>
    <string name="we_want_to_hear_your_ideas_and_suggestions">We want to hear your ideas and suggestions</string>
    <string name="leave_a_rating">Leave a rating</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show More</string>
    <string name="weather_prediction">weather prediction</string>
    <string name="no_rain_is_expected_this_week">No rain is expected this week</string>
    <string name="treat_your_plant_safely">Treat your plant safely with growers of the world</string>
    <string name="rate_the_green_defend_app">Rate the Green Defend app</string>
    <string name="checking">Checking</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_send_the_latest_offers_from_the_green_defend_application">I agree to send the latest offers from the Green Defend application</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="introduce_yourself_to_others">Introduce yourself to others</string>
    <string name="always_be_happy">Always be happy</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="diagnostic_results">Diagnostic results</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>
    <string name="communication">Communication</string>
    <string name="please_enter_code">Please Enter Code</string>

    <!--    desha-->
    <string name="q1_1">What are the main vegetables grown in the world?</string>
    <string name="a1_1">The main vegetables grown in global cuisine include rice, corn, barley, potatoes, peanuts, beans, cotton, and sugars</string>
    <string name="q2_1">What are the types of microenvironments for vegetable growth?</string>
    <string name="a2_1">Vegetables vary in their basic elements, but in general they need a wide variety of nutrients in large quantities and sunlight in general</string>
    <string name="q3_1">What is the component you want in vegetable yield?</string>
    <string name="a3_1">Many factors affect crop productivity, including conditions, soil, fertilization, water management, pests and diseases</string>
    <string name="q4_1">What is the importance of vegetable diversity in agriculture?</string>
    <string name="a4_1">Versatile in improving soil health, preventing diseases and pests, increasing biodiversity, and improving the health of agricultural systems</string>
    <string name="q5_1">How can farmers control crops with pests and diseases?</string>
    <string name="a5_1">Farmers can protect crops from pests by using advanced agricultural techniques, such as sub-agriculture and chemical application by specialists, adhering to agricultural principles, and adopting integrated management practices</string>
    <string name="q6_1">What is the importance of using supplements in crop farming?</string>
    <string name="a6_1">It helps to reduce modern quantities such as hydroponics, climate glass, and modern agriculture in comprehensively increasing and reducing resources such as water and agricultural areas</string>
    <string name="q7_1">What items do you want for the quality of your crops?</string>
    <string name="a7_1">There are many factors that affect the quality of crops, such as soil, climate, fertilization, agricultural care, and sound agricultural practices</string>
    <string name="q8_1">How can farmers improve crop quality? </string>
    <string name="a8_1">Farmers can improve crop quality by selecting multi-insulation elements, providing necessary protection for plants such as irrigation and fertilization, and effectively managing pests and diseases</string>
    <string name="q9_1">What are the basic steps for growing vegetables successfully?</string>
    <string name="a9_1">The basic steps include choosing the appropriate site, preparing the soil, additional finer parts, necessary protection for the plants, etc. for growth and development</string>
    <string name="q10_1">What future challenges might crop cultivation face?</string>
    <string name="a10_1">Among the challenges that will change in the future are the shortage of water resources, changes in the causes of diseases and damages, and the demand for growing population crops</string>
    <string name="q11_1">What is the importance of genetic diversity in vegetables?</string>
    <string name="a11_1">Genetic diversity helps highlight the diversity of variations and circumstances of young players, and also contributes to highlighting diversity such as diversity and quality</string>
    <string name="q12_1">How can farmers determine the best crops to grow in their area?</string>
    <string name="a12_1">Farmers can obtain local climate and breeding data, consult with nutritional experts, and examine various types of vegetables that grow well in their area</string>
    <string name="q13_1">What technology is used in crop improvement?</string>
    <string name="a13_1">The technology used includes developing weather-resistant seeds, small-scale conditions, cutting-edge technology, logo-post-small, and artificial intelligence applications</string>
    <string name="q14_1">What materials are used to control pests and diseases using pesticides?</string>
    <string name="a14_1">Its uses include the use of insect pests, bumblebees, as well as beneficial fungi, permaculture, crop insects, and organic farming techniques</string>
    <string name="q15_1">What are the benefits of practicing farming and cropping practices?</string>
    <string name="a15_1">Practicing farming practices, naturally maintain good health, the effects of climate change, improve the quality of crops and improve their resistance to pests and diseases</string>
    <string name="q16_1">What is the importance of smart crop cultivation in improving crop production? </string>
    <string name="a16_1">The smart agricultural system relies on distinctive technologies and important data to analyze micro-conditions and needs of vegetables, which helps improve agricultural care and increase its diversity</string>
    <string name="q17_1">What are the economic and environmental benefits of adopting Indian farming practices? </string>
    <string name="a17_1">Economic benefits include reducing agricultural costs in the long term and increasing farmers ability to adapt to small challenges. The multiple benefits include biodiversity, water and soil diversity</string>
    <string name="q18_1">How can farmers improve soil quality for growing crops? </string>
    <string name="a18_1">Farmers can improve soil quality by using fertilization, soil conservation practices such as crop rotation, and improved irrigation and drainage</string>
    <string name="q19_1">What is the importance of organizing agricultural dates in growing crops? </string>
    <string name="a19_1">It helps to determine agricultural dates at precise periods for planting vegetables and provide similar conditions for their growth, which leads to an overall increase in the presence of crop regulation</string>
    <string name="q20_1">How can farmers benefit from technology in marketing crops? </string>
    <string name="a20_1">Farmers can use technology such as the Internet and social media to promote their products with customers, and choose diverse methods such as the Internet and mobile applications</string>
    <!-- امراض النبات -->
    <string name="q1_2">What is the importance of knowing plant diseases for farmers?</string>
    <string name="a1_2">Knowledge of plant diseases is crucial for farmers to take appropriate preventive measures and deal with them effectively, which helps protect crops and ensure productivity.</string>
    <string name="q2_2">What are the basic signs that indicate the presence of diseases in plants?</string>
    <string name="a2_2">Basic signs may include leaf damage, fungal spots, curling, stunting, loss of color, and other abnormal changes in the overall appearance of the plant.</string>
    <string name="q3_2">What are the effective ways to prevent plant diseases?</string>
    <string name="a3_2">Effective methods for preventing plant diseases include practices such as regular crop rotation, reducing agricultural intensification, using biological disinfection, and using resistant varieties.</string>
    <string name="q4_2">What are common fungal plant diseases and how can they be dealt with?</string>
    <string name="a4_2">Common fungal plant diseases include fungal decay, mold, rust, mildew and creeping mildew. It can be dealt with through the use of chemical or organic fungicides and the use of appropriate cultivation practices.</string>
    <string name="q5_2">What are common bacterial plant diseases and how can they be dealt with?</string>
    <string name="a5_2">Common bacterial plant diseases include bacteriophage, bacterial death, and bacterial stunting. It can be dealt with by using bacterial pesticides and reducing transmission of infection using clean agricultural tools.</string>
    <string name="q6_2">What are the common viral plant diseases and how can they be dealt with?</string>
    <string name="a6_2">•Common viral plant diseases include plant paralysis, yellowing and stunting. It can be dealt with by using resistant varieties and reducing the transmission of infection by insects that transmit the viruses.</string>
    <string name="q7_2">How can farmers diagnose and treat plant diseases effectively?</string>
    <string name="a7_2">Farmers can diagnose diseases by observing signs and symptoms and consulting agricultural experts. Diseases are treated by using appropriate biological or chemical pesticides and following recommended agricultural practices.</string>
    <string name="q8_2">What preventive measures can be taken to prevent the spread of plant diseases?</string>
    <string name="a8_2">Important preventive measures include: disinfecting agricultural tools after each use, maintaining the cleanliness of the farm and the surrounding environment, avoiding planting infected plants, and providing good ventilation to reduce excess moisture that may contribute to the spread of diseases.</string>
    <string name="q9_2">What are the symptoms that may indicate the presence of several plant diseases?</string>
    <string name="a9_2">Symptoms can include, for example, the appearance of brown or white spots on the leaves, curling of the leaves, swelling of the roots, and discoloration of the leaves in abnormal colors.</string>
    <string name="q10_2">How can farmers develop an integrated program to prevent plant diseases?</string>
    <string name="a10_2">Growers can develop a program that includes scheduling plantings on a regular basis, monitoring plants regularly to detect any early signs of disease, documenting problems and resolving them quickly, and training farm labor to effectively respond to plant problems.</string>
    <string name="q11_2">What types of plants are most commonly affected by diseases?</string>
    <string name="a11_2">The types of plants that are susceptible to diseases vary depending on the environment and growing conditions. Among the common plants that are susceptible to diseases are: vegetables such as tomatoes and peppers, fruits such as perennial fruits and bananas, ornamental plants and weeds.</string>
    <string name="q12_2">What are the important steps to monitor plant diseases at different stages of plant growth?</string>
    <string name="a12_2">Plants must be monitored regularly from the early stage of growth, and during all stages of growth, including the flowering and fruiting stage, in order to early detect any signs of disease and take the necessary preventive and remedial measures.</string>
    <string name="q13_2">ما هي أهمية استخدام البذور المعالجة والنباتات المقاومة في الحد من انتشار الأمراض؟</string>
    <string name="a13_2">The use of treated seeds and resistant plants can reduce the spread of diseases by reducing the use of chemical pesticides, thus reducing environmental pollution and reducing costs.</string>
    <string name="q14_2">What are the key steps to effectively get rid of diseased plants?</string>
    <string name="a14_2">Plants infected with diseases should be removed immediately and measures taken to prevent transmission of infection to healthy plants, such as properly disposing of plant waste and carefully cleaning agricultural tools.</string>
    <string name="q15_2">What steps must be taken to reduce the transmission of diseases by insects, birds and wind?</string>
    <string name="a15_2">Transmission of diseases by insects, birds, and wind can be reduced through the use of methods such as the use of agricultural nets, protective covers, and regular disinfection of equipment. Agriculture can also be organized appropriately to reduce the transmission of diseases by wind.</string>
    <!-- مراقبه النبات  -->
    <string name="q1_3">What is the purpose of monitoring plants in agriculture? </string>
    <string name="a1_3">The goal of plant monitoring in agriculture is to determine the health of plants, detect potential diseases, and improve the selection of crop presence</string>
    <string name="q2_3">How can modern constraints be used in plants? </string>
    <string name="a2_3">Modern details such as remote sensing, photography, and smart sensors can be used to monitor plant health, and study important data to reveal minute details in growth and development</string>
    <string name="q3_3">What is the importance of AI applications in plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a3_3">AI applications help analyze data more clearly and quickly, allowing data to be released and guided into plants and to reveal potential capabilities</string>
    <string name="q4_3">What techniques are used in remote sensing to monitor plants? </string>
    <string name="a4_3">This includes the use of drones and satellites equipped with technical sensors to measure the electromagnetic spectrum, such as infrared and ultraviolet radiation</string>
    <string name="q5_3">How can growers use data generated by plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a5_3">Farmers can use data to improve farm management and make more effective agricultural decisions, such as scheduling irrigation, applying fertilization, and early monitoring of pests and diseases</string>
    <string name="q6_3">What are the main challenges facing using modern technologies in plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a6_3">Among the main challenges are the cost of modern technologies, the difficulty of analyzing large data effectively, and ensuring accurate readings and correct interpretation of data</string>
    <string name="q7_3">What are the expected benefits of using modern technologies in plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a7_3">Among the expected benefits are increased productivity, improved crop quality, reduced costs and risks associated with pests and diseases, and improved use of resources such as water and fertilizers</string>
    <string name="q8_3">How can farmers overcome the challenges in using modern technologies in plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a8_3">Farmers can overcome challenges by investing in training and learning to use new technologies, collaborating with experts and specialists in the field, and choosing technological solutions that suit their needs and resources</string>
    <string name="q9_3">What are the basic steps to apply AI in plant monitoring? </string>
    <string name="a9_3">The basic steps include collecting relevant data about plants, training AI models using this data, and applying the trained models to predict the condition of plants and detect unusual patterns</string>
    <string name="q10_3">How can the use of new technologies in plant monitoring affect the future of agriculture? </string>
    <string name="a10_3">The use of modern plant monitoring technologies is expected to contribute to improving the efficiency of agricultural production and reducing environmental damage, leading to a more sustainable and productive future for agriculture</string>
    <string name="q11_3">What are the basic signs that can be monitored to determine the health of plants?</string>
    <string name="a11_3">Signs such as leaf color, plant growth, and any abnormal signs such as rot or wrinkling can be monitored</string>
    <string name="q12_3">What are the common pests that can be monitored and identified on plants?</string>
    <string name="a12_3">Common pests include: leaf-eating insects, molds, fungi, and pests that live in the soil.</string>
    <string name="q13_3">How can a farmer identify nutritional deficiencies in plants and deal with them?</string>
    <string name="a13_3">Signs such as discoloration of leaves or crossing between leaves can be used to determine nutritional deficiency, and can be treated by adding appropriate fertilizers</string>
    <string name="q14_3">What are the effective ways to control insect pests and fungal diseases naturally?</string>
    <string name="a14_3">Biological methods such as the use of predatory insects and positive bacteria, as well as the application of organic materials such as neem oil can be used to control pests.</string>
    <string name="q15_3">How can we determine the ideal irrigation periods for plants without relying on modern technologies?</string>
    <string name="a15_3">The soil can be monitored to determine its moisture content and watered when needed, in addition to relying on plant phenotypic signs such as wilting.</string>
    <string name="q16_3">What are simple ways to determine plant growth and detect any problems in development?</string>
    <string name="a16_3">The length, size, and development of leaves and fruits can be monitored to determine plant growth and identify any problems.</string>
    <string name="q17_3">How can we provide effective care for plants in the face of harsh weather conditions such as drought or frost?</string>
    <string name="a17_3">Plants can be protected using protection methods such as plastic cover to retain moisture in case of drought, or using plant covers to protect plants from frost.</string>
    <string name="q18_3">What are the basic steps that must be followed to preserve the soil and the environment surrounding plants?</string>
    <string name="a18_3">This includes practices such as agricultural rotation, maintaining vital soil, and reducing the use of chemical pesticides.</string>
    <string name="q19_3">How can a farmer provide protection for plants from harmful environmental factors such as strong winds or excessive heat?</string>
    <string name="a19_3">Natural barriers such as trees can be used to reduce the impact of wind, and provide shade to protect against extreme heat.</string>
    <string name="q20_3">What basic steps should be taken to deal with any emergency conditions that affect plant health, such as floods or fires?</string>
    <string name="a20_3">Plants at risk should be evacuated in emergency situations such as floods, and fire prevention measures such as removing accumulated dry vegetation should be taken.</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Enter Comment</string>
    <string name="no_permission_granted">No Permission Granted</string>
    <string name="not_select_image">Not Select Image</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="enter_comment">Enter Comment</string>
    <string name="wind_speed">Wind Speed</string>
    <string name="c">C</string>
    <string name="like">Like</string>
    <string name="unlike">unlike</string>

    <string name="description">description:</string>
    <string name="treatment">treatment:</string>
    <string name="prevention">prevention:</string>
    <string name="reason">reason:</string>
    <string name="comment">comment</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New  Password</string>
    <string name="enter_current_password">Enter Current Password</string>
</resources>